<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Showdown</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Showdown</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 15:59:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Country Picker</title>
      <link>http://example.org/country-picker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 15:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/country-picker/</guid>
      <description>Flow Country Picker The Flow country picker is a javascript module that can be loaded on any website. It exposes the function window.flow.countryPicker.createCountryPicker which takes in an options object that will define its behavior. By default the country picker module will utilize the local Flow session cached in the browser or API calls to determine a list of countries to display. These behaviors can be changed via options provided to the country picker module.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow Features</title>
      <link>http://example.org/flow-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 22:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/flow-features/</guid>
      <description>Flow Features Flow allows organizations to create features whose values are determined by the country or exprience of their customers. The values can either be a boolean (true or false) or a text string. Features can be created in Console by following the Features link under Organization Settings.
Dynamically insert text based on the country or experience Using string features in Flow implementors can easily associate text with a country or experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habits</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 16:36:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/habits/</guid>
      <description>There was an Old Person whose habits, Induced him to feed upon rabbits; When he&#39;d eaten eighteen, He turned perfectly green, Upon which he relinquished those habits.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Herse</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/the-herse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 16:33:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/the-herse/</guid>
      <description>There was an old man in a hearse, Who murmured, &amp;quot;This might have been worse; Of course the expense Is simply immense, But it doesn&#39;t come out of my purse.&amp;quot;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flapper</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/the-flapper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 16:19:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/the-flapper/</guid>
      <description>A nifty young flapper named Jane While walking was caught in the rain. She ran--almost flew, Her complexion did too, And she reached home exceedingly plain.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>